# Angelina Tabakaeva



#### Contact

#### Address:

**Dubai, United Arab Emirates** 

#### **Phone:**

+971 52 463 52 99

#### Email:

tabakaeva4u@mail.ru

#### **Nationality:**

Russian

### Languages

Russian - Native

English - Fluent

# **Luxury Goods Professional**

### Summary

I consider myself a person with a positive attitude, confident, flexible, mature and with a friendly disposition. I enjoy helping others and giving outstanding service.

Due to my work experience within the customer service field, I have learned how to deal with different people in a decisive way. The interaction with different nationalities had given me exposure and skills to manage different situations to positive outcomes and best results for Company profit and benefits.

## Skills Highlights

- Time management
- Strong sales skills
- Luxury goods sales
- Sales strategy
- Customer satisfaction
- Customer interaction
- Innovative
- Service-focused
- Target oriented

# Experience

Sales Executive - 01/2019 to Present Arnold and Sons LLC, Dubai, UAE

- Dealing with VIP clients and Royal families, VIP customer database
- Achieving sales targets by brand on quarterly and yearly basis
- Building contacts with potential clients to create new business opportunities
- Keeping prospective client database updated
- Making international and national calls for new business leads
- Presenting the Brand per company rules and standards
- Maintaining knowledge of overseas recruitment offered by the company
- Arranging meetings with prospective clients
- Following company guidelines and procedures for acquisition of customers
- Attending sales and Brand related trainings and then applying the same with customers in order to be able to meet set standards at AS&S

#### Senior Sales Representative - 11/2017 to 12/2018 AWRostamani Lifestyle, Dubai, UAE

- Delivering excellent customer service
- Ensuring launch of new collections to be displayed in time
- Displaying and merchandised products as per guidelines and the Brand standard
- Creating an attractive environment conductive to selling and purchasing
- Establishing the atmosphere, ensuring neatness and pleasingly arranged displays

# Senior Sales Associate- 07/2014 to 10/2017 Chopard Boutique, Dubai, UAE

- Delivering excellent customer service
- Assisting customers with the choice of the Brand products
- Merchandising and managing stock and transfers
- Training juniors staff
- Working with documentation warehouse transfer in and out, inventory check up

#### **Boutique Supervisior**- 03/2013 to 05/2014 **Luxury Fashion (Fendi, Burberry, TL)** Doha, Qatar

- Assisting the manager in day-to-day operations of the Boutique
- Educating clients on products and promoting the brand
- Organizing schedules ensuring staff works equal shifts and have equal work load
- Taking full responsibility for the safe and efficient operation
- Administrating stock counts and coordinating completion of annual stock take
- Maintaining and developing good relationships with existing clients

#### Sales Executive- 07/2010 to 10/2012 Luxury Multibrands Boutique, Russia, Moscow

- Educating clients on products represented in the store
- Providing feedback on customer preferences, stock levels
- Maintaining correspondence with established clients and developing new client list
- Executing stock and inventory control, arranged stock transfers

### Education

**Bachelor of International Relations** 2007 to 2011 **Kyrgyz-Russian Slavic University** 

### Certifications

- Sales Techniques, Dubai, UAE :09/2014 to 12/2014
- Luxury goods, leather goods: UAE 07/2018-09/2018
- Diamonds and Precious Stones Specialist: UAE 01/2019
- Customer service and Brand development: 02/2016 to 04/2016
- Course of Starting and Developing a New Enterprise in University in Cardiff, England: 09/2013